<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xml:base="/rss/updates.xml" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:foaf="http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/" xmlns:og="http://ogp.me/ns#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:sioc="http://rdfs.org/sioc/ns#" xmlns:sioct="http://rdfs.org/sioc/types#" xmlns:skos="http://www.w3.org/2004/02/skos/core#" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#">
  <channel>
    <title>USA.gov Updates</title>
    <link>/rss/updates.xml</link>
    <description>Government news and featured content from the U.S. government's official website, USA.gov.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    
                <item>
                    <title>Have an Emergency Plan for Disasters</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:14:25</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/have-an-emergency-plan-for-disasters</link>
                    <description>Every minute counts during a disaster – plan now so you’re prepared. Know the risks about the different disasters and hazards that could affect you and your family where you live, work, and go to school.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Five Things to Know About the Supreme Court</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:16:27</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/five-things-to-know-about-the-supreme-court</link>
                    <description>Brush up on your Supreme Court expertise with USAGov’s five facts to know about the nation's highest court.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Eight Steps to Patent Your Invention</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:20:14</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/eight-steps-to-patent-your-invention</link>
                    <description>Have you invented something new, useful, and non-obvious, and want to patent it? Patenting an invention can be challenging, but the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office can help.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Recognize The Signs of Suicide and Find Help</title>
                    <pubDate>Jun 08, 2018 15:45:15</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/recognize-the-signs-of-suicide-and-find-help</link>
                    <description>Suicide is the second leading cause of death in people between the ages of 15 to 34 in the United States, according to a new study from the Centers for Disease Control (CDC).</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov's Guide to the Fourth of July</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:18:37</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagov-s-guide-to-the-fourth-of-july</link>
                    <description>Each year Americans celebrate what many call the “nation's birthday” with firework shows, parades, and patriotic ceremonies. Here’s USAGov’s list of ways to celebrate Independence Day.
</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov's Fireworks Safety Tips for the Fourth of July</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:21:37</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagov-s-fireworks-safety-tips-for-the-fourth-of-july</link>
                    <description>Follow these tips when using fireworks to ensure you and your family have a fun and safe Fourth of July.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Get Help with Living Expenses</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:26:33</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/get-help-with-living-expenses</link>
                    <description>Learn about federal government benefit programs for low income earners that can help pay for food, housing, healthcare, and other expenses.
</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s 6 Things to Know Before You Start Paying Off Your Student Loans</title>
                    <pubDate>Sep 29, 2020 12:27:20</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-6-things-to-know-before-you-start-paying-off-your-student-loans</link>
                    <description> Here are six great tips from StudentAid.gov that can help you start the process of paying off your student loans.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Preventing Addiction: Share Your Story</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:27:11</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/preventing-addiction-share-your-story</link>
                    <description>During National Prevention Week, May 13-19, the Substance Abuse and Mental Health Services Administration (SAMHSA) encourages families to take action today for a healthier tomorrow. 
</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Protect Yourself and Your Money Every Day</title>
                    <pubDate>Dec 09, 2021 08:53:24</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/protect-yourself-and-your-money-every-day</link>
                    <description>Stay safe and informed, know what to do when a purchase or service goes wrong, and how to address it by visiting USA.gov.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Kids and Depression</title>
                    <pubDate>Aug 17, 2021 10:48:26</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/kids-and-depression</link>
                    <description>Learn the signs and risk factors for depression in teens and younger children and find out how you can help them heal.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Start the School Year Off Right with USAGov’s 8 Tips for 2018</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:11:53</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/start-the-school-year-off-right-with-usagovs-8-tips-for-2018</link>
                    <description>Are you and your kids ready for the new school year? Back to school season can be an expensive, busy, and stressful time — these tips may be able to help.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s Voting Guide for Military Members and Americans Abroad</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:08:14</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-voting-guide-for-military-members-and-americans-abroad</link>
                    <description> If you’re an American living abroad or a member of a military family it doesn’t mean you have to put your vote on hold. It just means that your voting process will be a little different. 
</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s Guide for First Time Voters</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:06:20</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-guide-for-first-time-voters</link>
                    <description>Are you a new voter? Maybe you’re turning 18, or you decided to get involved in the electoral process for the first time in your life. Either way, there’s a lot to learn. 
</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Eight Tips to Be Ready for Hurricane Florence</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:04:32</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/eight-tips-to-be-ready-for-hurricane-florence</link>
                    <description>Hurricane Florence is bringing heavy wind and rain to large parts of the East Coast in the coming days. Here are recommendations for how to prepare and survive the storm.
</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Recovery after Hurricane Florence</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:02:53</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/recovery-after-hurricane-florence</link>
                    <description>Hurricane Florence has brought heavy wind and rain to large parts of the East Coast. Stay informed on the latest warnings, advisories, and the path of Florence with bulletins from the National Weather Service.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s Guide for Voters with a Disability </title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:01:17</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-guide-for-voters-with-a-disability</link>
                    <description>This Election Day, millions of Americans will visit a polling location to exercise their constitutional right to vote. </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s Guide for Seniors</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:46:50</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-guide-for-seniors</link>
                    <description>In honor of Older Americans Month, these tips can help empower you to meet the challenges of getting older and make the most of life.

</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Find Veterans Day Volunteer Ideas</title>
                    <pubDate>Nov 09, 2018 13:15:45</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/find-veterans-day-volunteer-ideas</link>
                    <description>Veterans are a major part of any American community and it's important to make sure they're not left behind. Volunteers help vets every day, and Veterans Day is the perfect occasion to give back. </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Online Shopping this Holiday Season? Keep Your Credit Card Information Safe</title>
                    <pubDate>Nov 09, 2018 14:30:00</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/online-shopping-this-holiday-season-keep-your-credit-card-information-safe</link>
                    <description> Unfortunately, there’s no 100% failproof solution. But there are some things you can do to protect yourself during the Black Friday and Cyber Monday sales and beyond.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>The Gettysburg Address, 155 Years Later</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 18:57:57</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/the-gettysburg-address-155-years-later</link>
                    <description>On November 19, 1863, President Abraham Lincoln delivered a speech during a ceremony to dedicate a cemetery to Union soldiers killed at the Battle of Gettysburg.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s 2018 Guide to Holiday Shopping</title>
                    <pubDate>Nov 19, 2018 14:00:15</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-2018-guide-to-holiday-shopping</link>
                    <description>The holiday shopping season is one of the busiest times of the year, with many opportunities to buy gifts for family and friends, and chances to donate to charitable causes.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Support for Families When A Suicide Attempt Hits Home</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:53:53</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/support-for-families-when-a-suicide-attempt-hits-home</link>
                    <description>Find resources that could help you and your family after a suicide attempt by a loved one.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s Five Tips to Get Great Deals from Government Auctions and Sales</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:58:46</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-five-tips-to-get-great-deals-from-government-auctions-and-sales</link>
                    <description>You may have heard that you can buy “stuff” from the government. But how does it work? Can you really get good deals?</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Bouquets and Bruises: This Valentine’s Day, Help Someone Experiencing Abuse</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:51:00</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/bouquets-and-bruises-this-valentines-day-help-someone-experiencing-abuse</link>
                    <description>If you want to support a friend in this difficult situation, or if you need support yourself, USAGov has gathered these resources to help.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Free, Official Sources to Find Unclaimed Money</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:49:23</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/free-official-sources-to-find-unclaimed-money</link>
                    <description>There might be unclaimed funds or property waiting for you from savings or checking accounts, wages and pensions, tax refunds, insurance policies, and more.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>This Valentine’s Day Help Someone Experiencing Abuse</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:31:31</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/this-valentines-day-help-someone-experiencing-abuse</link>
                    <description>If you want to support a friend in this difficult situation, or if you need support yourself, USAGov has gathered these resources to help.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>A Healthy Prescription For a Healthy Home</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:27:52</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/a-healthy-prescription-for-a-healthy-home</link>
                    <description>Feeling ill? Some health issues could be connected to the health of your home. Learn how to give your home a checkup. </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Fourth of July: How to Properly Display the American Flag</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:45:17</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/fourth-of-july-how-to-properly-display-the-american-flag</link>
                    <description>This guide and infographic from USAGov, based on the Federal Flag Code, can help you show respect for the flag as you celebrate America’s 241st birthday. </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Leaving the Military? Avoid Job and Education Scams</title>
                    <pubDate>Apr 05, 2022 15:28:40</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/leaving-the-military-avoid-job-and-education-scams</link>
                    <description>Most servicemembers transition out of the military into a civilian career or educational training. </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Four Tips for Holiday Giving</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 18:55:01</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/four-tips-for-holiday-giving</link>
                    <description>Use these tips from USAGov to help make your donations count and celebrate the holiday spirit of giving.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Navigating Power of Attorney: How to Help Loved Ones Manage Their Money</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 20:00:09</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/navigating-power-of-attorney-how-to-help-loved-ones-manage-their-money</link>
                    <description>Be informed and prepared to take your legal duties when a power of attorney is granted to you.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Taking the Mystery Out of Getting a Mortgage</title>
                    <pubDate>Feb 08, 2019 16:15:00</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/taking-the-mystery-out-of-getting-a-mortgage</link>
                    <description> First time home buyers can learn how to start the process of getting a mortgage, what loan options exist, and more.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Fighting Back Against Sexual Harassment in Housing</title>
                    <pubDate>Feb 19, 2019 11:30:45</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/fighting-back-against-sexual-harassment-in-housing</link>
                    <description>Finding housing can be stressful, especially if money’s tight, you’re on your own, and you don’t have a lot of options.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s 5 Apps to Download Now</title>
                    <pubDate>Sep 01, 2020 15:05:41</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-5-apps-to-download-now</link>
                    <description>Check out USAGov’s list of the top five government apps to download now.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Is an Unclaimed Tax Refund Waiting for You?</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 18:51:12</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/is-an-unclaimed-tax-refund-waiting-for-you</link>
                    <description>Many lower income earners may not even realize they’re eligible for special tax credits or a refund. Don’t miss out on money that’s yours.
</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Inspire Action and Change Lives</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 18:44:16</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/inspire-action-and-change-lives</link>
                    <description> Each year, people around the U.S. share creative and innovative ways to highlight substance abuse prevention and positive mental health initiatives.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s Apps to Download in 2018</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:32:52</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-apps-to-download-in-2018</link>
                    <description>Ordering food, shopping, reviews and buying movie tickets, there’s an app for everything. Download these in 2018. </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Get Ready for Class with USAGov’s 2019 Back To School Checklist</title>
                    <pubDate>Aug 13, 2019 11:12:24</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/</link>
                    <description>Content</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s Tips for Safely Enjoying America’s National Parks</title>
                    <pubDate>Jun 19, 2020 17:41:29</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-tips-for-safely-enjoying-americas-national-parks</link>
                    <description>Whether it’s a quick drive or camping for a whole week, time spent at a national park can turn any ordinary day into an unforgettable experience with friends and family. 
</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Apply for a Passport in Person at an Event Near You</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 18:41:42</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/apply-for-a-passport-in-person-at-an-event-near-you</link>
                    <description>Getting ready to travel abroad in 2020? Before you book flights, look for attractions, and explore places to eat during your trip, be sure you have a passport. </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Caring for Caregivers: Resources from USAGov Help in Difficult Times</title>
                    <pubDate>Dec 15, 2020 13:38:25</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/caring-for-caregivers-resources-from-usagov-help-in-difficult-times</link>
                    <description>It’s easy to feel overwhelmed when you’re caring for a parent, spouse, or child with medical needs. </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Be More Travel Savvy: Join Us for a Travel Twitter Chat on 9/24/19</title>
                    <pubDate>Sep 16, 2019 11:45:30</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/be-more-travel-savvy-join-us-for-a-travel-twitter-chat-on-9-24</link>
                    <description>Join us on Tuesday September 24 at 1PM ET to learn about travel 
preparation. Bring your questions about passports, applications, 
airport lines, vaccines before traveling, and more. </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Be More Travel Savvy: Join Us for a Travel Twitter Chat on 9/24</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 18:40:55</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/be-more-travel-savvy-join-us-for-a-travel-twitter-chat-on-9-24</link>
                    <description>Join us on Tuesday September 24 at 1PM ET to learn about travel preparation. Bring your questions about passports, applications, airport lines, vaccines before traveling, and more. </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s Back to School Guide for Teachers and Parents  </title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:43:57</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-back-to-school-guide-for-teachers-and-parents</link>
                    <description>Back to school time can be both exciting and stressful for parents and teachers alike. </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Test Feature</title>
                    <pubDate>Nov 12, 2019 09:06:58</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/test-feature</link>
                    <description>Test feature</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s 2019 Guide to Holiday Shopping</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 20, 2020 09:40:35</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-2019-guide-to-holiday-shopping</link>
                    <description>Tips and resources to enhance the public's experience during the 2019 holiday shopping season.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Get Help for Homelessness, Hunger, and More</title>
                    <pubDate>Apr 30, 2021 08:43:03</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/get-help-for-homelessness-hunger-and-more</link>
                    <description>Every day, hundreds of thousands of Americans face homelessness and go without proper food and shelter. It can affect people at any age and from all walks of life. </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Primary Season is Almost Here</title>
                    <pubDate>Jan 29, 2020 09:10:05</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/primary-season-is-almost-here</link>
                    <description>It's almost here. The 2020 presidential primaries will begin in less than a month. It's important to keep track of key dates and deadlines, if you want to participate in this important process.

</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Six Scams to Be Wary of in 2020</title>
                    <pubDate>Feb 25, 2020 08:59:58</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/six-scams-to-be-wary-of-in-2020</link>
                    <description>If you’re convinced that scams only affect a particular group of people, think again. Sadly, millions of Americans are targeted by scammers every year. </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Have Questions About Scams? Join Our Twitter Chat on March 5</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 10:20:10</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/have-questions-about-scams-join-our-twitter-chat-on-march-5</link>
                    <description>Join the upcoming live Twitter chat on Thursday, March 5, 2020, at 11 AM ET for tips, important resources, and answers to your questions about scams and fraud.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Five Ways USAGov Can Help Your Family Connect in 2019</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 18:52:42</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/five-ways-usagov-can-help-your-family-connect-in-2019</link>
                    <description>For 2019, set goals to create an emergency plan, protect your credit, and expand your family knowledge and time together.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title> USAGov’s 2018 Guide to Holiday Shopping</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 18:56:49</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-2018-guide-to-holiday-shopping</link>
                    <description>The holiday shopping season is one of the busiest times of the year, with many opportunities to buy gifts for family and friends, and chances to donate to charitable causes.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Recognize The Signs of Suicide and Find Help </title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:23:11</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/recognize-the-signs-of-suicide-and-find-help</link>
                    <description>Suicide is the second leading cause of death in people between the ages of 15 to 34 in the United States, according to a new study from the Centers for Disease Control (CDC). </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Five New Year’s Resolutions that USAGov Can Help You Achieve</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:34:09</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/five-new-years-resolutions-that-usagov-can-help-you-achieve</link>
                    <description>If you're still looking for areas or goals to focus on in 2018, take some inspiration from USAGov’s New Year's Resolutions.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title> USAGov’s Guide to Holiday Shopping</title>
                    <pubDate>Nov 30, 2020 10:17:08</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-guide-to-holiday-shopping</link>
                    <description>As holiday shopping season starts, there are many opportunities to spend money on gifts for family and friends, and requests to donate to charitable causes.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>How to Fight Flu This Season </title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:37:05</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/how-to-fight-flu-this-season</link>
                    <description>Even healthy people can get very sick from the flu and spread it to friends and loved ones.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>This Is Just a Drill</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:38:20</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/this-is-just-a-drill</link>
                    <description>There has been confusion and rumors on social media about a U.S. Department of Defense drill that starts on November 4, 2017.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Preparation for Tomorrow Begins Today</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:39:36</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/preparation-for-tomorrow-begins-today</link>
                    <description>Your personal my Social Security account is one of the most powerful tools available to help you prepare for retirement.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Three Passport Life Hacks To Try Before 2018</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:41:05</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/three-passport-life-hacks-to-try-before-2018</link>
                    <description>Here are three things you should know to get the most out of your passport and your international travel experience.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>One Easy Place to Find Proof of Your Social Security Benefits</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:42:37</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/one-easy-place-to-find-proof-of-your-social-security-benefits</link>
                    <description>When you’re applying for a mortgage, loan or housing, you may need proof of your Social Security benefits.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Four Reasons Not to Put Off Signing up for a “my Social Security” Account</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:48:06</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/four-reasons-not-to-put-off-signing-up-for-a-my-social-security-account</link>
                    <description>April is National Social Security Month and USAGov has four reasons why signing up for an account now will help you later.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s Guide to Displaying the American Flag</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 16, 2020 19:52:18</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-guide-to-displaying-the-american-flag</link>
                    <description>This guide from USAGov, based on the Federal Flag Code, can help you show respect for the flag as you celebrate this Fourth of July.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s Tips for Safely Enjoying America’s National Parks in 2020</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 20, 2020 09:45:27</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-tips-for-safely-enjoying-americas-national-parks-in-2020</link>
                    <description>Whether it’s a quick drive or camping for a whole week, time spent at a national park can turn any ordinary day into an unforgettable experience with friends and family. 
</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Be Sure to Declutter Online This Spring Season</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 20, 2020 11:47:37</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/be-sure-to-declutter-online-this-spring-season</link>
                    <description>You may be ready to clean your kitchen or go through boxes in your closet, but have you thought about your digital clutter? </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Three Ways to Manage Your Stress</title>
                    <pubDate>Apr 27, 2020 14:38:07</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/three-ways-to-manage-your-stress</link>
                    <description>Everyone reacts differently to a stressful situation, but taking the steps to cope with the emotional and physical tensions of stress can change everything.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov: Your Guide to Reliable and Official Government Information</title>
                    <pubDate>Dec 23, 2020 13:21:51</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagov-your-guide-to-reliable-and-official-government-information</link>
                    <description>Finding reliable and official government information can be a challenge, especially if you don’t know where to start.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>4 Things You Should Know About the 2020 Census</title>
                    <pubDate>Dec 02, 2020 08:54:25</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/4-things-you-should-know-about-the-2020-census</link>
                    <description>Your response to the 2020 Census matters. But you may be unsure about what to expect. If you’re confused or simply want to know more, explore USAGov’s guide of things you should know before filling out the census.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov's Fourth of July Fireworks Safety Tips</title>
                    <pubDate>Jun 29, 2020 10:31:53</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagov-s-fourth-of-july-fireworks-safety-tips</link>
                    <description>Follow these tips when using fireworks to ensure you and your family have a fun and safe Fourth of July.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Get Help Paying Your Bills With USAGov</title>
                    <pubDate>Aug 05, 2020 11:14:04</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/get-help-paying-your-bills-with-usagov</link>
                    <description>If you have a low income or are experiencing financial hardship, federal government benefit programs may be able to help you pay for food, housing, health care, and other expenses. </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s Five Tips for Reporting a Scam</title>
                    <pubDate>Dec 09, 2021 09:04:13</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-five-tips-for-reporting-a-scam</link>
                    <description>Scammers target millions of Americans every year, and anyone can fall victim to their deceptive tricks. Last year, the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) received over 3 million reports of fraud. </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USA.gov’s Guide to Mental Health Resources From the Government</title>
                    <pubDate>Sep 28, 2020 17:26:45</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usa-govs-guide-to-mental-health-resources-from-the-government</link>
                    <description>Struggling with mental health challenges can make you feel isolated, frustrated, and overwhelmed. This guide from USA.gov can help you find resources to help.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Seven Tips to Stay Prepared for the 2020 Hurricane Season</title>
                    <pubDate>Sep 28, 2020 16:50:09</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/seven-tips-to-stay-prepared-for-the-2020-hurricane-season</link>
                    <description>The 2020 hurricane season lasts until November 30. According to predictions from the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), this season may be more active than previous years.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Online Safety in the Age of Digital Learning</title>
                    <pubDate>Sep 02, 2020 08:21:38</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/online-safety-in-the-age-of-digital-learning</link>
                    <description>Children in 2020 have different levels of experience with technology. Regardless of their expertise, prepare to discuss online safety with them. Consider the following tips from USAGov when teaching kids about staying safe online.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s Quick Guide to Voting in 2020</title>
                    <pubDate>Dec 03, 2020 16:19:56</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-quick-guide-to-voting-in-2020</link>
                    <description>Election Day 2020 is just about six weeks away. With voter registration deadlines approaching soon, it’s time to make sure you’re ready.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov Answers FAQs About Voting</title>
                    <pubDate>Dec 23, 2020 11:17:34</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagov-answers-faqs-about-voting</link>
                    <description>The coronavirus pandemic makes the 2020 election season different than any before it. And it’s leaving a lot of people looking for information on how, where, and when to cast their vote. </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>What’s the Difference Between Government Grants and Loans?</title>
                    <pubDate>Dec 22, 2020 16:46:01</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/whats-the-difference-between-government-grants-and-loans</link>
                    <description>Are you looking to get help paying for your education? Does your non-profit organization need financial assistance to complete a community project? The government offers financial help, but you may not know what’s available and where to find it. </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Get Help From USAGov This 2020 Holiday Season</title>
                    <pubDate>Feb 11, 2021 12:12:44</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/get-help-from-usagov-this-2020-holiday-season</link>
                    <description>The 2020 holiday season is one like never before. Due to the pandemic, people across the U.S. have adjusted the way they work, shop, and connect with others.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s Five Tips for the 2021 Tax Season</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 22, 2021 17:09:59</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-five-tips-for-the-2021-tax-season</link>
                    <description>As the tax season approaches, you may have questions about filing your federal, state and business taxes in 2021. Economic Impact Payments, tax credits and other relief provided in 2020 have many people wondering how to file during the pandemic.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s Five Lessons Learned to Combat Scams in 2021</title>
                    <pubDate>Apr 20, 2021 10:16:44</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-five-lessons-learned-to-combat-scams-in-2021</link>
                    <description>According to the Federal Trade Commission, Americans have reported over 260K scams and lost over $412M in frauds linked to COVID-19. Due to the rise in fraud, federal experts across the government share official information on how to recognize, avoid and report many types of scams.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Important Tips to Prepare Before and During a Hurricane</title>
                    <pubDate>Aug 31, 2021 17:27:48</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/important-tips-to-prepare-before-and-during-a-hurricane</link>
                    <description>Having an annual hurricane checklist is key to ensuring your family’s safety during this time of year to prepare yourself, your family, and your assets. Here are a few things to remember.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s Guide To Government Benefits During Any Life Event</title>
                    <pubDate>May 05, 2021 08:15:20</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-guide-to-government-benefits-during-any-life-event</link>
                    <description>People navigate life, not government. Yet there are many life events that are associated with government benefits.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>What to Expect From Passports and International Travel in 2021</title>
                    <pubDate>Aug 09, 2021 14:27:11</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/what-to-expect-from-passports-and-international-travel-in-2021</link>
                    <description>Many people are planning destination getaways, visits with families, and business trips in the next year. If you need to renew or get a new passport, you may need more time than you think. </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Five Tips to Recover After a Hurricane</title>
                    <pubDate>Sep 13, 2021 12:20:14</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/five-tips-to-recover-after-a-hurricane</link>
                    <description>Hurricane Ida created storm surge, flooding and tornadoes that impacted thousands of people across the country. If you or a loved one are in an affected area from major storms this year, follow these tips to return home, stay safe and get assistance where you need it. </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>What Information and Services Does the U.S. Government Offer in Spanish?</title>
                    <pubDate>Sep 16, 2021 14:28:17</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/what-information-and-services-does-the-u-s-government-offer-in-spanish</link>
                    <description>To commemorate Hispanic Heritage Month, USAGov en Español, the official website of the U.S. government in Spanish, in collaboration with government agencies is launching a public engagement campaign to publicize the programs and services offered in Spanish.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s 2021 Guide to Holiday Shopping</title>
                    <pubDate>Nov 18, 2021 15:31:23</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-2021-guide-to-holiday-shopping</link>
                    <description>The holiday shopping season is one of the busiest times of the year. There are many opportunities to buy gifts for family and friends, donate to charitable causes and shop at stores in person and online. USAGov offers you tips to make the most of your holiday budget and protect yourself from scams and fraud.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s Guide to Navigating Travel to the U.S.</title>
                    <pubDate>Dec 21, 2021 09:01:41</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-guide-to-navigating-travel-to-the-u-s</link>
                    <description>Are you planning an international trip in the next few months? USAGov, your official guide to government information, can help you navigate the latest changes in travel requirements. </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s Tips to Jumpstart Your 2022</title>
                    <pubDate>Jan 19, 2022 10:31:20</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-tips-to-jumpstart-your-2022</link>
                    <description>As the days unfold into the new year, it can be hard to prioritize the things that need to be done first. If you’re unsure of where to begin, USAGov has reminders of what government programs and information to add to the top of your list.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s Tips to Jump-Start Your 2022</title>
                    <pubDate>Jan 20, 2022 07:44:18</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-tips-to-jump-start-your-2022</link>
                    <description>As the days unfold into the new year, it can be hard to prioritize the things that need to be done first. If you’re unsure of where to begin, USAGov has reminders of what government programs and information to add to the top of your list.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Protect Yourself From the Ways Love Can Go Wrong</title>
                    <pubDate>Feb 09, 2022 12:27:13</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/protect-yourself-from-the-ways-love-can-go-wrong</link>
                    <description>Valentine’s Day is a great opportunity to show the people in your life love, care and what they mean to you. Unfortunately, the excitement and romance of it all can have a bad side. If you or a loved one is looking for love online or experiencing domestic violence, know how to stay safe from the ways love can go wrong.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Six Tips for the 2022 Tax Season</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 29, 2022 21:26:46</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/six-tips-for-the-2022-tax-season</link>
                    <description>As the federal tax deadline approaches soon, you may still have questions about filing your federal, state and business taxes in 2022. Use USAGov’s tax season guide to understand steps you need to take to successfully file by the April 18 deadline.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Understand Government Benefits for Different Stages of Life</title>
                    <pubDate>May 05, 2022 16:47:31</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/understand-government-benefits-for-different-stages-of-life</link>
                    <description>Every phase of life has unique challenges that can change at any time. As you experience big transitions like retiring from a long career or losing your home, understand what government services can help along the way. Search through the latest guide to navigate through any event life throws your way.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Four Government Apps for Times of Emergency</title>
                    <pubDate>Aug 05, 2022 09:21:01</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/four-government-apps-for-times-of-emergency</link>
                    <description>These days, there are mobile applications for every situation that help make your life easier. Did you know there are apps developed for you by the U.S. government to prepare before, stay safe during and recover after an emergency? </description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Get Answers to Your Travel Questions</title>
                    <pubDate>Aug 31, 2022 11:25:20</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/get-answers-to-your-travel-questions</link>
                    <description>Since a lot has changed with travel during the pandemic, know the latest requirements and recommendations from experts across the government. Follow this guide for answers to your latest travel questions before you go.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Prepare for Election Day 2022</title>
                    <pubDate>Oct 31, 2022 09:28:32</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/prepare-for-election-day-2022</link>
                    <description>Election Day 2022 is almost here. Get ready with quick tips from USAGov. This checklist will arm you with the things you need to know so you can vote in person or by mail.
</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>Get the Help You Need to Pay Your Bills</title>
                    <pubDate>Nov 21, 2022 12:44:14</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/get-the-help-you-need-to-pay-your-bills</link>
                    <description>If you are experiencing financial hardship, federal government benefit programs may be able to help you. See what you and your family could be eligible for, the type of temporary financial support you can receive, and how to apply.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>USAGov’s 2022 Guide to Holiday Shopping</title>
                    <pubDate>Nov 17, 2022 08:51:28</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/usagovs-2022-guide-to-holiday-shopping</link>
                    <description>USAGov offers you tips to make the most of your holiday budget and protect yourself from scams and fraud.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>What Programs and Services Are Available for Veterans?</title>
                    <pubDate>Feb 14, 2023 13:31:31</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/what-programs-and-services-are-available-for-veterans</link>
                    <description>Members leave the military and return to civilian life every year. But life after the military can present many difficult and unique challenges. If you are experiencing financial hardship or transition struggles, know there are resources that can help.</description>
                </item>,
                <item>
                    <title>The 988 Lifeline and Other Mental Health Services</title>
                    <pubDate>Mar 09, 2023 10:20:51</pubDate>
                    <link>https://www.usa.gov/features/the-988-lifeline-and-other-mental-health-services</link>
                    <description>Mental health continues to pose a challenge to millions of people.  Understand the options you have to face your mental health struggles and get the support you need.</description>
                </item>
</channel>
</rss>